International Union of Immunological Societies records
International Union of Immunological Societies records
- Series I. Officers & Council, 1966-2011; 1971-1997 bulk; 23 boxes (9.5 linear feet)
  - Subseries I.B. Countil Meetings, 1970-2010; 4.5 boxes (2 linear feet)
    - 2009 Minutes (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - 2010 Minutes (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - 2011 Minutes (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Subseries I.C. Reports, 1971-2000; 1980-1990 bulk; 1.5 boxes (.75 linear feet)
    Reports of the Treasurer, President, and Secretary-General arranged by office and then in date order.
    - Treasurer 1971 (1st International Congress, Budget) (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Treasurer 1973 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Treasurer 1980 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Treasurer 1981 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Treasurer 1982 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Treasurer 1983 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Treasurer 1984 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Treasurer 1985 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Treasurer 1986 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Treasurer 1987 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Treasurer 1988 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Treasurer 1989 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Treasurer 1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Treasurer 1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer 1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Treasurer 1995 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - President 1977 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - President 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Secretary-General 1988 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Secretary-General 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Secretary-General 2000 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Subseries I.D. Miscellany, 1985-2001, undated; 1 box (.5 linear feet)
    Miscellaneous administrative documents and photographs arranged by type of document
    - Archives Correspondence 1993-1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Committee Review Correspondence 1998 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Statutes n.d. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Manual of Operations n.d. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Newsletter 1985-1987 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Photos and Related Documents (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Secretarial/Professional Management of Organization Bids and Correspondence 1999-2001 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Nominations of Officers and Council Members 1998-2001 (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Nominations of Officers and Council Members 1998-2001 (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Subseries I.E. Accounting, 1972-1998; 6 boxes (2.5 linear feet)
    Financial records including ledgers, bank statements, invoices, receipts, reports, audits, and correspondence arranged in alphabetical order by subject and then in date order.
    - ALAI (Associacao Latino Americana de Imunologia) 1988 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Ledgers 1972 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1983 (acc# 7901.932:) (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1983 (acc# 7900.162) (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1985 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1986 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1987 (Jan - June) (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1987 (July - Dec) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1988 (Jan - Aug) (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1988 (Sept - Dec) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1989 (Jan – July) (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1989 (Aug – Dec) (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1990 (Jan – July) (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1990 (Aug – Dec) (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1991 (Jan – June) (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1991 (July – Dec) (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1992 (Jan – May) (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Bank Statements and Transfer Receipts 1992 (June – Dec) (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Income & Expenses 1990-1992 Summaries (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Income & Expenses 1993 Audited Accounts (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Income & Expenses 1993 CEG/Suisse (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Income & Expenses 1993 Merrill Lynch (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Income & Expenses 1993 Ontvangsten (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Income & Expenses 1993 Postbank (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Income & Expenses 1993 Solomon Hare (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Income & Expenses 1993 Summary (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Income & Expenses 1993 Uilbetalingen (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Income & Expenses 1994 Audited Accounts (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Income & Expenses 1994 Expenses (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Income & Expenses 1994 Income (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Income & Expenses 1994 Merrill Lynch (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Income & Expenses 1994 Postbank (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Income & Expenses 1994 Summary (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Income & Expenses 1995 Audited Accounts (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Income & Expenses 1995 Expenses (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Income & Expenses 1995 Income (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Income & Expenses 1995 Merrill Lynch (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Income & Expenses 1995 Postbank (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Income & Expenses 1995 Summary (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Income & Expenses 1996 Audited Accounts (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Income & Expenses 1996 Expenses (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Income & Expenses 1996 Income (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Income & Expenses 1996 Merrill Lynch (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Income & Expenses 1996 Postbank (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Income & Expenses 1996 Summary (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Income & Expenses 1997 Audited Accounts (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Income & Expenses 1997 Expenses (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Income & Expenses 1997 Income (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Income & Expenses 1997 Merrill Lynch (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Income & Expenses 1997 Postbank (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Income & Expenses 1997 Summary (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Clinical Immunology 1986-1988 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Clinical Immunology 1991-1997 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Education Committee 1988 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Education Committee 1991-1998 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - The Immunologist 1997 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Nomenclature 1988 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Nomenclature 1992-1997 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Standardization 1988 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Standardization 1992-1996 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Symposium Committee 1988 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Travel Expenses 1985-1986 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Veterinary Immunology Committee 1988 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Veterinary Immunology Committee 1992-1997 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Series II. Membership, 1971-2001; 7 boxes (2.75 linear feet)
  Correspondence, invoices, receipts, reports, and printed directories arranged in three subseries.
  - Subseries II.A. Member Payments, 1971-1966; 2.5 boxes (1 linear foot)
    Invoices and receipts for membership dues arranged in date order.
    - 1971 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - 1972 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - 1973 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - 1974 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - 1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - 1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - 1977 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - 1978 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - 1979 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - 1980 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - 1981 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - 1982 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - 1983 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - 1984 -1985 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - 1986 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - 1987 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - 1988 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - 1989 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - 1990 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - 1991 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - 1992 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - 1993 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - 1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - 1995 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - 1996 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Subseries II.B. Member Societies and Regional Federations, 1974-2001; 4 boxes (1.5 linear feet)
    Member correspondence, memos and reports arranged in alphabetical order by member organization.
    - ALAI 1989-1993 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - ALAI 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - ALAI 1997-2002 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Allergy and Immunology Society of Thailand 1990-1992 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Armenian Society for Immunology 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Australasian Society for Immunology Incorporated 1996-1998 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Austrian Society for Allergology and Immunology 1996 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Balkan Immunological Societies 1992-1995 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Bangladesh Society for Immunology 1994-1995 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Belarusan Society for Immunologists and Allergists 1997 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Brazilian Society for Immunology 1998 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Cameroon Immunological Society 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Chinese Society of Immunology 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Chinese Society of Immunology 1997 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Croatian Immunological Society 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Cuban Society for Immunology 1996 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Czechoslovakia 1979-1995 (Observers) (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - EFIS 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - EFIS 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - EFIS 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Egyptian Society of Immunology 1990 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - FAIS 1989-1992 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - FAIS 1993-1995 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - FAIS 1997-2000 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - FIMSA 1989-1993 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - FIMSA 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - FIMSA 1998-2001 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - German Society of Immunology 1998 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Hong Kong Society for Immunology 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Immunological Society of Asia and Africa 1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Immunological Societies of Eastern Europe 1992 – 1993 (Outreach) (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Immunology Society of Slovenia 1992-1997 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Kenyan Society of Immunology 1992 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Kyrgys Republic 1998 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Latvian Society for Immunology 1991 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Lithuanian Society of Immunology 1992 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Malaysian Society for Immunology 1998 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Paraguayan Immunological Society 1996 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Peoples Republic of China 1979-1986 (Observers) (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Phillipine Society of Allerology and Immunology 1997 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Romanian Immunologists 1989-1990 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Russian Society of Immunologists 1992-1998 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Singapore Society of Immunology and Rheumatology 1989 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - South African Immunology Society (SAIS) 1990-1992 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Taiwan 1979-1984 (Observers) (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Tanzania Society of Immunology 1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - USSR 1980-1985 (Observers) (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Yugoslavian Immunological Society 1992-2001 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Zairian Society of Immunology 1992 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Zimbabwe Society for Immunology 1991 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Member Societies 1977-1986 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Member Societies 1993 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Societies 1980-1986 (Observers) (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Issues 1990-1995 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Subseries II.C. Directories, 1982-1994; .5 box (.25 linear feet)
    Printed directories and working papers arranged by type of document and then in date order.
    - Printed Blue Books 1982, 1985, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Printed Blue Books 1993, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Working Papers and Lists 1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Working Papers and Lists 1992 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Working Papers and Lists 1994 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Series III. Meetings, 1970-2010; 1974-1995 bulk; 7 boxes (3 linear feet)
  Correspondence, agendas, minutes, reports, bids, budgets, invoices, receipts, programs, ephemera, and brochures pertaining to society meetings, conferences and congresses arranged by meeting title and date and subsequently by type of document.
  - International Congress of Immunology 1971: Organizing Committee Minutes 1969 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1974: General Assembly Minutes (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1974: Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1974: Reports, Agendas, and Programs (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1977: General Assembly Minutes (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1980: General assembly Minutes (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1980: Correspondence A – D (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1980: Correspondence E – Z (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1980: Reports, Agendas, & Programs (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1983: General Assembly Minutes (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1983: Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1983: Reports, Agendas, Programs, & Minutes (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1983: Reports, Agendas, Programs, & Minutes (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1983: Ephemera (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1983: Ephemera (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - International Congress of Immunology & 1st IUIS Conference on Clinical Immunology 1986: General Assembly Minutes (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - International Congress of Immunology & 1st IUIS Conference on Clinical Immunology 1986: Congress Planning and Arrangements (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - International Congress of Immunology & 1st IUIS Conference on Clinical Immunology 1986: Congress Planning Committee (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - International Congress of Immunology & 1st IUIS Conference on Clinical Immunology 1986: Congress Program & Registration Bulletin (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - International Congress of Immunology & 1st IUIS Conference on Clinical Immunology 1986: Correspondence 1980-1983 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - International Congress of Immunology & 1st IUIS Conference on Clinical Immunology 1986: Correspondence 1984 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - International Congress of Immunology & 1st IUIS Conference on Clinical Immunology 1986: Correspondence 1985 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - International Congress of Immunology & 1st IUIS Conference on Clinical Immunology 1986: Correspondence 1986 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - International Congress of Immunology & 1st IUIS Conference on Clinical Immunology 1986: Minutes & Contracts/Joint Meeting of IUIS Executive Committee and the Canadian National Committee (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - International Congress of Immunology & 1st IUIS Conference on Clinical Immunology 1986: Photographs (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - International Congress of Immunology & 1st IUIS Conference on Clinical Immunology 1986: Reports, Agendas, and Program (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1989: General Assembly Minutes (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1992: Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1992 General Assembly Minutes (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1992 Bursaries and Conference Budget (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1995: Arrangements (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1995 Bursaries (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1995: President’s remarks for opening ceremony. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1995: Programs, Announcements, & Registration Packet (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1998: Agenda and Election of IUIS Officers (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1998: Bursaries (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1998: Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - International Congress of Immunology 1998: Planning (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2001: Bids (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2001: Planning (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2001: Planning & Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2001: General Assembly Minutes (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Bids (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Bids (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Bursaries (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Ephemera (1 of 7) (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Ephemera (2 of 7) (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Ephemera (3 of 7) (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Ephemera (4 of 7) (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Ephemera (5 of 7) (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Ephemera (6 of 7) (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Ephemera (7 of 7) (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: General Assembly Minutes (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Media (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Media (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Planning (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Post Congress Publications and Thank You's (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Press Releases and Coverage (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Proposal (Montreal) (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2004: Proposal (Israel) (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2007: Bids (1 of 3) (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2007: Bids (2 of 3) (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2007: Bids (3 of 3) (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2007: General Assembly Minutes (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - International Congress of Immunology 2010: General Assembly Minutes and Conference Reports (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - International Immunopathological Symposium 1970: List of Participants (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Series IV. Committees, 1967-2000; 8 boxes (3.75 linear feet)
  Records pertaining to society committees organized into 9 sub-series by committee title.
  - Subseries IV.A. Organization, 1994-1995; 1 folder
    Correspondence related to the assignment of committee chairs and other organizational issues.
    - Committee Chairmen 1994-1995 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Subseries IV.B. Clinical Immunology, 1967-2000; 2 boxes (1.5 linear feet)
    Correspondence, minutes, articles and reports arranged in date order.
    - 1967-1969 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - 1970 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - 1971 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - 1972 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - 1973 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - 1974 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - 1975-1979 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - 1983-1982 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - 1993-1997 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - 1998-2000 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Subseries IV.C. Committion for Europe, 1972-1973; 1 folder
    Contains minutes, correspondence and a questionnaire.
    - 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Subseries IV.D. Education, 1974-1998; 4 folders
    Correspondence, minutes, reports and notes in date order.
    - 1974-1986 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - 1989-1998 (1 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - 1989-1998 (2 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - 1989-1998 (3 of 3) (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Subseries IV.E. Nomenclature, 1971-1998; 2 boxes (.75 linear feet)
    Reports, papers, correspondence and memos arranged in date order.
    - 1971-1973 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - 1974-1979 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - 1982 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - 1983 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - 1984-1986 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - 1990-1994 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - 1995-1998 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Subseries IV.F. Publication, 1985-2000; 3 folders
    Contains correspondence and memos.
    - 1985 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - 1992-1997 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - 1998-2000 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Subseries IV.G. Standardization, 1971-1998; .5 box (.25 linear feet)
    Correspondence files including reports, and drafts of papers are arranged in date order.
    - 1971 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - 1978 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - 1982 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - 1983-1986 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - 1990-1993 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - 1994-1995 (1 of 2) (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - 1994-1995 (2 of 2) (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - 1996-1998 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Subseries IV.H. Symposia, 1971-1991; .5 box (.25 linear feet)
    Agendas, correspondence and reports are arranges in date order.
    - 1971-1973 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - 1974-1980 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - 1981-1985 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - 1982 Ephemera (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Subseries IV.I. Veterinary Immunology, 1980-1998; 3 boxes (1.25 linear feet)
    Documents include reports, correspondence, conference and workshop planning documents, and files relating to the establishment of the committee. The sub-series is arranged alphabetical by file type and then chronologically.
    - Annual Reports: 1982-1990 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports: 1991-1998 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Avian Marker Workshops 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Budget & Reports 1986-1989 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Budget 1990-1994 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Budget 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence 1980-1989 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence 1990-1992 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence 1993-1994 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Education Program 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Immunoglobulins 1990-1992 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Liason with other groups 1986-1989 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Meetings Agendas & Minutes 1983-1998 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Meetings Correspondence 1986-1992 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Membership 1983-1992 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Pig CD Workshops 1991-1992 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Proposal for the Establishment of Veterinary Committee (1 of 3) (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Proposal for the Establishment of Veterinary Committee 1979-1980 (2 of 3) (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Proposal for the Establishment of Veterinary Committee 1980-1986(3 of 3) (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Publications 1993-1994 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Publications 1997-1998 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Reports 1983-2000 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Ruminant CD Workshop 1987-1990 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Standardization Correspondence 1985-1990 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Symposium, 1st International 1986 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Symposium, 2nd International 1989 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Symposium, 3rd International 1992 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Symposium, 4th International 1995 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Symposium, 6th International 2001 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Workshops 1983 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Workshops 1993-1994 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Workshops 1997-1998 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Series V. Affiliated Organizations, 1972-2000; 3.5 boxes (4 linear feet)
  Records pertaining to organizations with which IUIS has a working relationship are organized into subseries by organization.
  - Subseries V.A. European Federation of Immunological Societies (EFIS), 1973-2000; 4 folders
    Minutes, reports, correspondence and questionnaire responses are arranged in date order.
    - 1973-1976 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - 1977-1985 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - 1982 Ephemera (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - 1990-2000 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Subseries V.B. International Training and Research Center (ITR), 1977-1980; 1 folder